Yes, we get superpowers!
Superpowers!
There's a monster deep within your dreams.
Taking aim for your
heart so it would seem.
Stand tall and read, go to
hell and jump for paradise.
Every time dangerous, dangerous.
We like it serious, serious, oh.
Looking deep in the dream
there is the one in pain.
Turns out that's the one who
means the most to you today.
Adventure calls now, let's go.
The balls built between
us, they will show.
Still what we don't know.
Yes, working hard together.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Got to dream.
Despite the rivalry.
Gotta see it through.
Believing in you.
There's even charm in failure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
All the love and the tears.
In the world we're in.
United gently bringing up.
Our thought again, yeah.
We're the foolish ones we love.
We'll carry on till we see the light.
The sun will rise.
The greatest fight at its core.
Is against myself forevermore.
Come on, let's do it now, let's go.
The balls filled between
us, they will show.
So what we don't know.
That's what we call adventure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Got to dream despite the rivalry.
Gotta see it through believing in you.
There's even charm in failure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Superpowers.
Superpowers. Superpowers.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Superpowers.
I'm relieved we've made it to sea.
Now, if we can just get to the
sunny, we'll be sitting pretty.
Man, that was so good!
Wish I could enjoy it as much as you.
Everything's all slippery
now. Oh, no. Watch out.
We're trying to safety, little fishies.
Oh, ha.
Brooke, Brooke, is that a mermaid?
What? Where is she?
Wait, it's a mermaid.
Never mind.
Do you think he's fishing?
Get closer.
No, thanks.
I am not impressed. Let's go.
Oh, no!
It helps to sleep!
When Big Mom experiences her hunger
pains, it is best to steer clear.
I believe you.
But what are they?
A blind frenzy.
Nothing can stop her unless
she consumes what she craves.
Until then, no one is
safe from her rampage.
Where's my game?
She's unreachable in this state.
It seems this time she desires
a piece of wedding cake.
She didn't even get a bite at the tea
party, so she's likely fixated on that fact.
You see?
You shouldn't have ruined it for her.
I did pull it off, though, didn't I?
And hey, at least I got to have
plenty of yummy cake. Yeah!
You're eating it, mid-plan?
Mwah!
And it was super yummy!
Uh, whatever.
I hope the sunny isn't much further.
I can't tell if we're
getting close or not.
This forest is so annoying!
So do you guys think that
we're going the right way now?
Hey, look!
That river's kind of familiar, right?
I'm pretty sure the sunies should
be right there on the other side.
Wait a second.
Wasn't that the bridge that
got shattered by the crocodile?
Oh, yeah.
We can't trust anything.
The entire forest is our enemy.
Every step we take,
it's trying to fool us.
I'm sure they're moving the landscape
around to throw us for a loop.
This place may seem familiar.
However, I highly doubt
that this is the same spot.
Lola's Viva card won't get
us out of this one, sadly.
Not when Mama herself
is right on our heels.
All the more reason to keep laying that
bait down, though, Nami. I'm on it.
Oh, Zeus!
We cannot allow Zeus to return to Mama.
Otherwise, there's truly no escape.
Get over here, Zeus!
Right now!
Hurry, everybody, or she's gonna
catch up to us! Good movie!
I'm in big trouble!
Hey! Huh?
Oh, hey, Meridius!
Well, Zeus, why are you disobeying
Mama's orders? Answer me!
Zeus, look over here!
I got a nice juicy weather egg full
of storm clouds with your name on it!
Whoa, that's for me?
Oh, come on!
Get back here, you idiot!
Hey, you! Sun guy!
Huh?
You're gonna pay!
You shouldn't have
burned up that tree guy!
Get ready!
That's our Lock!
No way!
So sorry, buddy.
But you're gonna need to
take me down some other way.
Government hockey's not working!
He's worse than a logeotype!
I'm gonna burn all of you to a cliff!
Oh, that's fun!
Come help, Mom.
Give me a sec.
Can't you see I'm busy here?
I just want one more bite
of Stormcloud for the road.
More.
Jinbei! Hurry!
Get across the bridge, everyone!
Okay!
Spirit wave!
Did it work?
Certainly.
He's just a massifier, after all.
A little juice to the
face does the job handily.
You bastard.
It's him!
Prepare yourselves, Straw Hats.
You won't be leaving here alive.
Welcome to your final resting place.
You'll all die!
What?
How did they beat us here?
The homies must have rearranged
the entire landscape.
We're surrounded.
Then I suppose that leaves
us with no other option.
Yeah, it's time to kick their asses!
Hey, Pedro, I think I saw
you five years ago, right?
Crap!
Silly rabbits!
No!
Get off me!
You okay, Tablet?
Worry about yourself first!
Knobla Shamba!
Let's go!
Here goes!
Good job!
Eagle bazooka!
Don't get separated.
We have to keep running.
Right.
Understood.
Hey, Luffy, grab Kara. Okay.
There's no escape!
Sit down!
Take this!
Watch out!
Back off!
Ugh!
Okay!
We're in big trouble.
Mind it, Betty.
What the?
He devoured it.
Uh, that isn't right.
So delicious!
my weather egg it's inside Zeus now what
is that clown doing this is a real mess
hey knock it off
hey we're over here sorry to
have kept you guys waiting
oh Aw.
Those don't look like our friends.
Just the opposite, I would say.
My apologies, but I'm afraid
that your friends aren't here.
New screen tip-out!
No!
Oh, no!
You think they're okay?
Go, go, go.
It would appear that Mama finished
off your friends with Zeus.
She'll be here soon, no doubt.
He can't be serious, can he?
He must have survived. Yeah.
Don't you worry. They're fine.
Lick.
Damn shame you didn't get to say goodbye.
Such frivolous optimism.
Then tell me, what will
happen when no one shows up?
Are you going to take the ship from us?
Honestly, if you want to
lickety-split in that submarine,
I don't mind turning my
head if it's only you two.
We decline.
Kong Fu fighter!
Get off of our ship!
The Sunny belongs to us!
So you wanna fight.
No bones about it.
We'll take back the
Sunny one way or another.
Then you're about to take a licking lick.
We've got a full house.
Shall we get this show started? I'm ready!
The forest, what happened here?
I hope they're all okay.
Hey, Robin, hurry up.
You got it.
I know it's a lot to ask.
I'm so sorry.
Don't be silly.
Besides, it's been a long time
since we made a cake together.
We'll do it.
You're going?
Is this a joke?
Budgie, I've told you.
The Straw Hat saved Loneless Life.
This is the least I can do to repay them.
Please chiffon—it's dangerous;
he'll be worried sick!
Listen
to him.
You should come with us.
We can't leave without you, ma ’am.
Come back already!
I refuse.
And I know how dangerous it'll be.
It's easy to say.
Thank you for saving Lola, but
that's just a hollow gesture.
I can finally pay them back.
The real test of character is
proving you mean what you said.
But sweetheart, you're
always a man of your word.
So you understand right, sweetie?
I need you to promise me one thing.
If I?
I
If I don't return, take care of Pez!
Jafar!
Come back safely, male!
I'm going to help you, Nami.
And return home to my family.
Big Sis! I see him!
Pudding, were you even listening just now?
Sa-sanji is...
Sa-sanji...
He's running away like a rat! You okay?
That was powerful!
My climb attack doesn't normally
shoot lightning that strong.
It wiped them all out.
Where's Big Mom?
Surely that hit her.
She's most likely in that massive hole.
So does that mean we actually
knocked her out cold?
What the heck?
Wado?
That's definitely her.
Just as I feared.
Kay!
How is she alive?
Our mistake.
We shouldn't have assumed
she'd go down that easily.
She's trying to get out!
Maybe it's too deep and she's stuck?
Then let's run while we still can! Agreed.
We don't have to win.
We just have to escape.
I'm afraid that won't
keep her busy for long.
Jinbei's right!
That's not good.
Her hunger pangs won't
subside on the road.
There's no stopping her.
There's my king!
Hurry, run!
Oh no, the ground's giving way!
Get ready!
Bring me my wedding cake!
I know you have it!
You have my cake!
Give it to me!
She's climbing out.
Straw Hats, up here.
Pudding, Siobhan?
Pudding, what'd you want?
Are you here to trick us again or what?
You can stop Mama's
hunger pangs with my help.
It's an obvious trap.
I knew I should have tied
her up in the first place.
Please just listen to me!
Hold up, but why is Siobhan with her?
I thought she ran off with Benji.
I want to start...
Like me!
Would you shut up?
Just let me finish.
Oh, my dear Pudding, you're okay.
Your pretty little face is unharmed.
I'm so happy.
Get it together, Pudding.
Hurry, Big Mom's closing in.
Mama, get to the point before
everyone here ends up dead.
You're useless!
You deserve death, you miserable idiots!
Huh?
Even if you do make it out to sea,
Mama will hunt your
crew down in cold blood
and watch you all sink
into the murky depths!
Hey, what did you just say?
Wrong, pudding!
What are you talking about?
What am I saying?
You're right, you're right, I'm sorry!
Listen, Mama believes that you
guys stole her big wedding cake.
She's completely fixated on
that idea right now. Huh?
There is no cake.
We don't have it.
Yes, I know.
But as of right now,
Mama would chase you to
the ends of the world
just to get one bite
of that sweet dessert.
Exactly. Give up, Sanji.
Come stand at my side and savor
this momentous occasion with me.
We'll watch your friends
perish in Mama's hands.
What is your deal?
Would you cut that out?
I'm ruining the plan.
I'm such a wreck.
If you came here to torture
us, you can get lost, you jerk.
Wait a minute.
That's not it.
Hey, black-legged Sanji. Go ahead.
Not for nothing, but Pudding told me
you're really good at making sweets.
Uh-huh.
But I'm first class at anything I make.
That's perfect.
Then you have to help us bake a cake.
The exact one Mama wants
so we can stop her.
Then we'll help all of you guys
escape. But why? You were free.
Because I still owe you
one for saving Lola.
I'll risk my life to repay you.
No complaints. Thanks a ton. Uh-huh.
Ha!
Who knows if we'll survive or not.
But I'll make one thing clear.
I'm not doing this for you.
It's sheer luck that the cake I wanted
to bake is the same one Mama craves.
And I just passed by
this area by coincidence.
I didn't know you people would be around.
So don't go thinking I
came all the way here to
stop her because I didn't
want to see you all die,
you understand me? Sanji!
She's all over the place!
Anyway, back to business.
So where can we bake this cake?
All the ingredients we need
can be found in Chocolatown.
The plan is for the
three of us to head there
immediately and bake the
cake as fast as we can.
Then we'll carry it back by boat
and pass it to the Straw Hats.
That should get it to Mama,
who will no doubt be after you.
The cake will serve as a diversion.
You'll just have to hold out
until we're finished baking.
Is that her?
Be warned that once you set
sail, enemies will swarm you.
But I have faith that you'll
be able to pull through.
We will.
Okay, then.
I'll go with you.
Perfect.
Hop on, quickly.
Hang on a second.
Who said I was giving you
a lift, you pathetic dummy?
No.
I can't!
Big Mom, get out of the hole.
We're counting on you,
because I don't think anything short of a
perfect cake will put
an end to this rampage.
Okay then, I'm going to leave you guys
for now, but I promise I'll be back.
Yeah!
You got this!
I'm not worried!
Hey, Pony, ship on!
She's doing it again!
Get away!
You wanna tell me what the
two of you are doing here?
Luffy, I'll meet up with you and see!
That wasn't a promise, Sanji!
Ikaku!
You're kidding me?
That was too close for comfort.
Everyone, can you stand?
Let's go.
We gotta hurry back to the Sunny now.
Wait, that's not the way.
Robin, go back down again.
Head to where we were before, then
fly straight for the coastline.
Roger that.
Hey, Straw Hats!
That's not the way.
You're all headed straight into a wall.
Hold on a sec.
Are you nice, Pudding, now?
I was certain we were
headed towards the sea.
I suppose we've been fooled
yet again. Follow me.
The coast is this way.
Okay, let's go!
You'll never leave!
Let me handle this for you.
Memory filament!
And now, flashbacks!
Oh yeah, I've got some
groceries to pick up.
My big brother bust me in the head.
Wanna go for walkies, good girl!
I haven't seen my son in three weeks.
Oh, where could he be?
What's going on here?
We must use this to our benefit.
Let's hurry!
What happened?
Memories from the soul's original owners
have come flooding back to the homies.
But just as a warning, the
effects won't last forever, okay!
While they're confused, they will
no longer be under mama's control.
So your crewmates and other allies
can get out of the forest safely now.
That's clever.
Nice work, Pudding
The hell?
How long have you been there, Sanchi?
Not long, I guess
What?
Didn't you notice?
Anyway, let's head to Chocolat Town and
make this cake Get off and swim, you idiot!
Your eyes are beautiful
even when you're angry
Huh?
You gonna be okay?
I'm fine!
Don't pull that crap on me!
Or else I'll wring your
neck next time, Sanji!
Honey!
All right, I see the coast
up ahead! Let's hurry!
We're almost there.
Hey, do you Karoo think Pudding
is really on our side now?
Well, I'm unsure,
but we'd better not let our guard down
until we're out of their territory.
You'll die here.
Come on, Zeus.
What the hell's gotten into you, huh?
Why'd you go and attack us, you big dummy?
I'm sorry, but I didn't really
have a say in the matter.
I don't want to hear your dumb excuses.
Don't ever let me catch you
doing that again. Right.
I heard you. Jeez.
That lightning cloud shirt was tasty.
I'd love to get another nibble. Huh?
You've been back a whole two minutes
and you're losing it already.
Don't disobey Mama again.
I know.
Get over here.
Give. Me. Back. My. Wedding. Cake. Now!
Watch out!
Everyone get down!
What a pain!
That attack nearly got us!
Thank you for the save, Jinbei!
You were quite effective against
the Chess Peacekeepers, Skeleton.
Did you just catch on?
I'm the Soul King, baby.
The Mirror.
That's where they're all coming from.
It's from Nami and Robin's room.
You think they'll get mad if we break it?
Let's ask for forgiveness later.
Shatter it to pieces!
And who exactly are you
going to apologize to?
You did see the lightning
earlier, didn't you?
Your crew is on its last lickety leg.
You know it's not too lickety
late to take me up on that offer.
I made no matter how hard
you try you'll never be
able to keep up with our
endless droves of soldiers.
You'll collapse long before the waves
stop pouring out of that mirror.
I'm not an unreasonable man though.
Submit now and I'll at
least spare your life.
Your friends are dead.
Let it go already.
Are you done talking to yourself yet?
What a foolish question!
I am tired of repeating myself.
I'll ask you once again
to get off this ship.
The Sunny belongs to
the Straw Hat Pirates.
You're absolutely certain you
want to go down this path?
Very well, then.
Who am I to complain if my enemies
don't happen to value their own lives?
Since you're begging me, I shall give
you both the sweet taste of death.
We can head straight to Kaku Island now!
Brooke! Chopper!
Wait a minute, isn't that your ship?
Damn it, it looks like
they're getting attacked.
They set up an ambush woefully fast.
Oh no, my big brothers are there!
They must be targeting Sanji's crewmates.
That'll teach ya!
Your friends are dead!
They were no match for
my darling brothers.
You shouldn't have let those
weaklings defend for themselves.
fool really back there pudding i can't
believe i actually said all that out loud
and what do you want to do
should we drop you off down
there it's fine more important
for me to help you all right
if you're sure we'll just keep
on moving forward then the
thing about my friends is You
don't need to worry about them
Knowing those guys, they'll be just fine
So let's do this we're gonna
knock out big mom with this cake